Passion. Seduction. Betrayal. Lily wanted to be just like Ivy.
Poison Ivy 2: Lily is a drama, romance, thriller film directed by Anne Goursaud.
A young and naive college art student becomes obsessed with assuming the identity and personality of a departed coed who used to live in
her room, and in so doing causes complications that result in two men, a student and her art professor, lusting after her.
Lily Leonetti, played by Alyssa Milano.
Gredin, played by Johnathon Schaech.
Donald Falk, played by Xander Berkeley.
Angela Falk, played by Belinda Bauer.
Daphne Falk, played by Camilla Belle.
Tanya, played by Kathryne Dora Brown.
Poison Ivy II: Lily is a 1996 American direct-to-video erotic thriller film
directed by Anne Goursaud, written by Chloe King and stars Alyssa Milano.
It is a sequel to the 1992 film Poison Ivy and the second
installment of the Poison Ivy film series.
The film explores themes of obsession, diary, sequel, murder, lust.
The tone is emotional and intense.